Ivan Chornyi

Senior Software Engineer

Skype: i.chorniy
Telegram: i_chornyi
Linkedin: ichornyi

About Me

Hi, my name is Ivan and I'm a Senior Software Engineer. My main passion is software development but this is not my single interest, I also like DevOps related challenges. I love to learn and use new technologies and approaches in practice. Technology-agnostic. I always work for the result. I always think before doing something. Glad to know that my work makes life easier for someone. 6+ years development experience. Strong communication skills. Google Associate Cloud Engineer Certified

Skills

Programming languages: PHP, Python, Javascript

Additional technologies: OOP, HTML, CSS, Typescript, Various API's

Frameworks/CMS: Symfony, Laravel, Phalcon, Codeception, Magento 1.x CE/EE, Wordpress,

Django, Flask, Angular X, NodeJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Selenium

Technologies: Websocket, AJAX, REST

Tools: PhpStorm, PyCharm, NetBeans, VSCode, Atom, Sublime Text, Git, Docker, Kubernetes,

Vagrant, Ansible, Terraform, Bash, SSH

Support Tools: Jira, Confluence, Pagerduty, HP LoadRunner

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Memcache, PostgeSQL, BigQuery

Operating Systems: Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, Raspbian, OS X

Servers: Nginx, Apache, GCP, AWS

Foreign languages: English(intermediate)

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks

Experience

SoftServe

DevOps Engineer

www.softserveinc.com

April 2021 - May 2022

MWDN

SRE

August 2020 - April 2021 mwdn.com

SoftServe provides services in the fields of big data, Internet of things, cloud computing, DevOps, e-commerce, computer security, experience design, and health care.[4] With its United States headquarters in Austin, Texas and European headquarters in Lviv, Ukraine, the company employed more than 10,000 people in offices in 2021.

As a member of CloudOps team I participated in various number of activities such as: strategic infrastructure/automation development, support of incoming requests from developers, support of Data department. Tech stack:

- GCP
- Terraform
- k8s
- CircleCI/Spinnaker

MWDN is an international development company with headquarters in Israel and development center in Kharkiv, Ukraine. Founded in 2002 by highly skilled project managers, MWDN has developed a significant number of successful projects concerning complex medical systems and cardiac monitoring in the past decade and a half. MWDN is also very proud of cooperation with some of the most successful international startups and a great experience in medical, web and mobile software development.

Participated as a member of the Cloud SRE The team is responsible for maintaining the medical imaging systems infrastructure and administering the GCP. My main responsibilites:

 compliance monitoring system development and maintenance for GCP infrastructure

2/5 https://ivan.chornyi.rocks

GlobalLogic

Senior Software Engineer

October 2016 - August 2020 globallogic.com

Ronis Business Tools

PHP Developer

August 2015 - September 2016

- development of application for synthetic monitoring of webapplications
- cost-savings automation for GCP
- infrastructure monitoring automation

GlobalLogic is a Digital Product Engineering Services company that was founded in 2000 and is headquartered in San Jose, California. It is a privately held company funded by Partners Group and CPP Investment Board. GlobalLogic provides software product development services, including experience design, complex systems engineering, content engineering, and self-contained engineering labs.

Development, maintenance and optimization of CRM for Forex brokers and various support and internal tools. Servers setup and optimization. Bugfix. CRM modules development from scratch. On-call technical support experience. Experience in upgrade PHP 5.5->7.1->7.4. The CRM core totally rewritten due been optimization purposes. Migration from AWS to GCP. Development of internal tools using Django/Flask.

Regular business trips. Half a year of experience in the role of Team Lead. Direct communication with customer.

Ronis is a leading eCommerce development agency that specialises in high converting Magento sites. Founded in 2003, our experienced team build stand-out, successful retail platforms for brands and small businesses.

E-commerce development:

- Development of new Magento(1.x CE and EE) websites
- E-store development and support/maintenance

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 3/5

roniscommerce.com

- API integration (email marketing, analytics and internal custom API's)
- Development of new internal services (like URL shortener, social network, product management tool)
- Bug fixing
- Support
- · Database optimization
- Internal synchronizations development

Fullstack development company. Outsourcing short-term projects.

Development of a wide range of web applications:

- · Code implementing and optimization
- Adding new functionality
- · Requirements clarification
- Bug fixing
- Support

Smythisoft

Junior PHP Developer

September 2014 - August 2015 smithysoft.com

Education

National University of Radioelectronics

Computer science & Biotechnical medic systems

2006 - 2011

Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics (NURE) is a higher education institution of the highest level of accreditation in Ukraine. It is one of the oldest technology universities in Ukraine, with over 7000 students and 30 scientific centers.

During my time at NURE I learnt most of my key skills that have I have taken through my career such as teamwork and working to tight deadlines. I spent a lot of my free time as a committee member of my faculty taking on *headman* role.

A Little More About Me

Date of birth: 29.09.1989

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 4/5

- Married
- Founder of Ukrainian Nissan Rogue Club

Alongside my interests in networks and software engineering some of my other interests and hobbies are:

- 3D printing
- FPV Drone racing
- USA Cars
- Online shopping
- World digitizing

Ivan Chornyi - References on request

https://ivan.chornyi.rocks 5/5